### **CONTACT**

# Lovelyo Yeremia Mokalu

Dewi Sartika Street 36, Cawang, DKI Jakarta, Indonesia.

Mobile (WA): (+62)85813501033
Email: mokalulovelyo@gmail.com
Linkedin: Lovelyo Yeremia Mokalu
Github: https://github.com/lovelyoyrmia
Portfolio: https://lovelyoyrmia.com

### **SUMMARY**

I'm a **final year student** at **Gunadarma University** majoring in **Computer Science**. **Experienced** in **different Programming Languages**. Able to effectively **self manage** during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Backend Developer Internship - Investo Medika Asia

Feb 2023 - Present

- Work with the engineering team to develop APIs using **Django**.
- Manage server on AWS Cloud using EC2, S3, Cloudfront.
- Build some features using Websocket, Scheduler (Cron Job), and Postgresql.

#### Core Team Academic - Gunadarma I/O

Oct 2022 - Present

- Work with a team to manage programming events.
- Mentored new members to have a good understanding of Software Engineering and Machine Learning.
- Mentored new members with technical skills in Software Engineering and Machine Learning.

# **Software Engineer Internship** - Feedloop

Nov 2022 - Mar 2023

- Work with team sales to create **POC/Prototype** for clients.
- Managed Database Application using SQL.
- Work with Product Manager and UI Designer to solve clients problems.
- Collaborated with and Mentored by Co-Founder to develop an ERP application for clients.
- Testing Rest API LinkAja (payment gateway) using Express Js, Postman.

# **Software Developer** - Freelancer

Sep 2021 - Present

- Created Services API using Node Js (Express Js), Docker, Jest, ORM and Git.
- Designed Front-end Web Application using React Js, Javascript, HTML, and CSS.
- Served user's data using **SQL** and **Firestore**.

# Machine Learning Data Entry Internship at Finku (Financial Startup)

Feb 2022 - Nov 2022 (9 mos)

- Managing and labeling data using **PPOCRLabel**.
- Automate labeled data using Python, and Google Sheet.
- Pulled data from customers through Linkedin and checked if customers have a Linkedin Account.
- Helped Customer Experience team to pull data from customers who get rewards from Finku.

# **Machine Learning Trainee** by Bangkit Academy 2022 led by Google, Traveloka, Gojek & Tokopedia Feb 2022 - Jul 2022 (6 mos)

- Had a good understanding of **Basic Machine Learning Algorithms** to **Advanced**.
- Designed prediction models using Deep Learning (Image Classification, NLP, Time Series) in Tensorflow.
- Lead a team to build an Application that will predict Indonesian Food using Image Classification Algorithms and Transfer Learning

# **CERTIFICATIONS AND AWARDS**

• Top 50 of Kalibrr Codefest - Aug 2022

Coding competition held by Kalibrr.

• Tensorflow Developer Certified - Jul 2022

CNN, NLP, Time Series, Sequences.

Google IT Automation Professional Certificate - Feb 2022

Python Programming, Git, REGEX, Version Control.

• Tensorflow Developer Specialization Certificate - May 2022

Deep Learning, Transfer Learning, CNN, NLP, Time Series and Sequences.

### **PROJECTS**

• Dentika (Jun 2022 - Present)

A Clinic Management Website that allows users to book appointments to meet a dentist and doctors.

• Foedtra (May 2022 - Present)

An Android App using Flutter that will predict Indonesian Food and get nearby restaurants based on the result of the prediction model.

### AREA OF EXPERTISE

• Javascript, NodeJs, Python and Dart.

- SQL/Relational Database
- Microsoft Excel Proficiency
- Time Management

- Storing Problem Solver
- Resourceful
- Self-directed
- Self-motivated

# **COURSES**

### Amazon Web Services - 2021

- Data Analytics.
- Machine Learning Terminology and Process.
- Machine Learning Building Blocks.

# Alibaba Cloud - 2021

- Getting Started with Python.
- Advanced Python Programming.
- Flask Framework Python
- Landing AI Developer Learning

### **EDUCATION**

### **Gunadarma University**

• Computer Science (2019 - Present)

Relevant Coursework: Algorithms, Basic Programming, Probability and Statistics, Big data, Data Mining, Database Relational, Machine Learning, Computer Security System, Website Development, Game Development, Computer Graphics, and Smart City.